<resources>
    <string name="app_name">POS-App</string>

    <!--Product Name-->
    <string name="prodName0">Game and Watch</string>
    <string name="prodName1">Sega Game Gear</string>
    <string name="prodName2">Gameboy Advance</string>
    <string name="prodName3">DS</string>
    <string name="prodName4">PS Vita</string>
    <string name="prodName5">Steam Deck</string>
    <string name="prodName6">3DS</string>
    <string name="prodName7">PSP</string>
    <string name="prodName8">Nintendo Switch</string>

    <!--Product Description-->
    <string name="prodDesc0">
        Experience the pure, addictive gameplay that launched a revolution. Perfect for collectors and minimalist gamers alike,
        the Game and Watch series combines iconic 80s aesthetics with a built-in digital clock.

        Created by legendary designer Gunpei Yokoi, this series was "Nintendo's" first foray into portable gaming.
        Each unit featured a single, high-contrast LCD game and a built-in digital clock and alarm.

        Its minimalist design and "D-pad" innovation laid the foundation for handheld consoles.

        <i>It’s not just a console; it’s a timeless piece of Nintendo history that fits perfectly in your pocket!</i>
    </string>

    <string name="prodDesc1">
        Why settle for monochrome when you can play in full, vibrant color?
        The Sega Game Gear was years ahead of its time, featuring a stunning backlit display that brought arcade-quality action to the palm of your hand.

        Unlike its competitors at the time, the Game Gear featured a full-color backlit screen and a landscape orientation.
        It essentially packed the power of a Sega Master System into a handheld, allowing for vibrant, console-quality graphics on the go.

        <i>If you want high-intensity Sega classics with the power of a home console on the go, this is your machine.</i>
    </string>

    <string name="prodDesc2">
        The successor to the Game Boy Color, the GBA brought 32-bit "Super Nintendo quality" gaming to the palm of your hand.
        This specific model features the iconic ergonomic horizontal design and the classic translucent indigo/purple finish that defined early 2000s gaming.

        Relive the golden age of portable gaming with the Game Boy Advance.
        Featuring an ergonomic horizontal design for maximum comfort during long play sessions, this indigo classic delivers crisp, SNES-level graphics.

        It’s the ultimate way to play legendary titles like <i> Pokémon </i> and <i> The Legend of Zelda </i>.
    </string>

    <string name="prodDesc3">
        Sleeker, brighter, and more stylish than ever, the DS Lite is the pinnacle of the DS family.
        With its intuitive touch screen and massive library of innovative titles, it offers a gameplay experience you can’t find anywhere else.
        The Jet Black finish provides a premium, modern look for the sophisticated gamer.
    </string>

    <string name="prodDesc4">
        <i>Immerse yourself in the most beautiful handheld visuals ever created.</i>

        The PS Vita was a technical marvel for its time, boasting a gorgeous 5-inch OLED screen and dual analog sticks.
        The 1101 model (3G/Wi-Fi) represents "Sony's" push for high-end, "triple-A" gaming on the move, featuring a rear touchpad and incredible processing power.
        From cinematic adventures to indie gems, the Vita is the choice for gamers who demand high-end performance.
    </string>

    <string name="prodDesc5">
        <i>Take your PC gaming wherever you go.</i>

        The Steam Deck is a portable beast, capable of running the latest AAA titles with ease.
        Developed by Valve, the Steam Deck runs a massive library of Steam games using a custom AMD APU, featuring a 7-inch touchscreen, trackpads, and full-sized controls to play modern PC titles anywhere.
        Featuring customizable controls, haptic trackpads, and the full power of the Steam ecosystem, it’s the most versatile and powerful handheld ever made.
    </string>

    <string name="prodDesc6">
        <i>Step into a world of depth without the need for bulky glasses.</i>

        The Nintendo 3DS offers a magical 3D experience that brings your favorite characters to life.
        With its unique dual-screen layout and backward compatibility, it’s a gateway to thousands of incredible adventures in a stunning Aqua Blue finish.
    </string>

    <string name="prodDesc7">
        The original PSP changed the game by introducing the Universal Media Disc (UMD) for movies and games.

        <i>It is a portable entertainment center.</i>

        Watch movies, listen to music, and play high-fidelity games on its gorgeous widescreen display.
        With its premium build quality and expansive capabilities, the PSP remains the gold standard for stylish, portable media.
    </string>

    <string name="prodDesc8">
        The world’s most versatile console is ready for action.

        Whether you’re docked to your TV for a cinematic experience or using the Joy-Cons for a quick match on the bus, the Switch adapts to your lifestyle.
        It’s the home of multiplayer fun and the biggest hits in gaming—perfect for the modern gamer.
    </string>

</resources>